(Howard:)You fly to Moscow,
they take you to Kazakhstan.
Then you get in a Russian Soyuz rocket
which shoots you into a low earth orbit.
Or it just sits on the launch pad because
the Kazakhi mafia sold the rocket fuel...
...on the black market, heh.
(Bernadette:)Are those Russian rockets safe?
(Howard:)Safe as it can be...
...when it was buiIt by the folks
who brought you ChernobyI. Ha, ha.
(Leonard:)I'd like to propose a toast.
(Leonard:)The dream to go up into space
is one we all share...
(Leonard:)...and Howard's making that a reality.
We're all very proud of you.
(All:)Cheers.
- That was a lovely toast. Kudos.
- Thank you.
SimuItaneously, a festival
of cloying clichés. You sicken me.
(Howard:)You're really quiet. Is everything okay?
(Leonard:)Fine.
(Bernadette:)Just a little tired.
(Howard:)I hope not too tired because I'm feeling
particularly masculine right now.